gobble.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Gobble

#### 1\. Our Commitment to Privacy.

This notice describes our Privacy Policy. Protecting your privacy and the personal information you provide us is a top priority for Gobble. For this reason, we do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We want our users to fully understand what information we collect, how we use this information, and the steps we take to protect your personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the policies and procedures we have put in place to achieve this goal. By visiting this Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

For the convenience of our visitors, this Website may contain links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy, security, data collection, and distribution policies. 

#### 2\. What Information is Collected.

##### (a) Information You Provide to Us:

We collect any information you enter on our Site or that you give us in any other way. This includes personal information such as your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information and phone number. It may also include, but is not limited to, other information related to servicing your meal subscription such as your weekly meal choices, food preferences, preferred delivery day, and meal feedback. 

##### (b) Your Usage of Our Site.

We automatically track certain information about you based upon your use of our Site, as well as from your interaction with emails that we send to you. The personal information we automatically collect may include your geolocation and other data, including your IP address, browser type, device type, the webpage you visited before coming to our Site, pages you visited on our Site, time spent on those pages, when and for how long you visited the Site, and similar information, which we collect through cookies, and other technologies. The information we automatically collect may be associated with any personal information that you have provided to us. 

##### (c) Cookies.

We use “cookies” on certain pages of our Site. Cookies are small files that can be used to track a user’s steps or automatically generate a user’s password. Cookies allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session and help us personalize your Site experience. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Site. Most cookies are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You may decline our cookies if your browser permits, although your use of the Site will then be restricted. 

#### 3\. How and When the Information is Used.

We may use your information to provide basic functionality on our Site, such as displaying appropriate meal recommendations, processing and fulfilling your meal subscription, communicating about orders and their status, and personalizing the customer experience where possible. 

We may also use your information to contact you for informational or promotional purposes and provide customer service to you. 

We may use non-personally identifiable information collected to determine user demographics, interests, and behavior and may market Gobble products using this information, or by sharing it with partners. Gobble may also provide your non-personally identifiable information to contractors so that they can perform services for us, such as IT or analytics. We may also utilize service providers to assist us in aggregating customer information, and then share such aggregated non-personally identifiable information with prospective marketing partners, advertisers and others. 

Your personally identifiable information that you provide to us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information from our records and other sources. This information may be shared with service providers that perform analytics to help us improve our products and site, to market our services, and to identify new potential customers. These marketing service providers may share your name and contact information with their partners, but they will not identify you as a Gobble customer. We may also share this information with third parties with whom we offer co-branded or joint product and service promotions, but will be done so only under a confidentiality agreement at least as restrictive as the privacy provisions contained in this Privacy Policy. 

**If you prefer that we do not use and share your information in this way, please email us at optout@gobble.com.**

Gobble reserves the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to our users, such as phone, text, email or mail. By providing Gobble with your email, phone number, and postal address, you consent to our using such contact information to send you notices. You may opt out of certain notifications by using the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email to opt-out of receiving future emails, replying STOP to text messages, email us a request at sous@gobble.com, or by changing your account settings. To stop receiving notices, you can also send us a request by mail to: 

Gobble, Inc  
Attn: Marketing Department  
637 Natoma Street, Suite 5  
San Francisco, CA 94103  

#### 4\. Legal Requests

We cooperate with law enforcement authorities, as well as with other third parties, to enforce laws, intellectual property rights, and to prevent fraud. In response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your email address, login history, fraud complaints, and site use history, with or without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, we will not disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to protect our rights or to prevent imminent physical harm, financial loss or to report suspected past, present, or future illegal activity. Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose to a third party your information, including your email address, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. 

#### 5\. How We Protect Your Information.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you provide sensitive information (such as a credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. 

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of such information. If you have any questions about security on our Site, please contact us as at sous@gobble.com. 

#### 6\. Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

#### 7\. Changes to Privacy Policy.

If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our website. Any such changes will be effective 30 days from the time such new policies are posted, unless otherwise stated in the change. 

#### 8\. Effective Date

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 1, 2019.
